vincipark.be 2015-09-10

# VINCI Park, leading parking provider, managing 2,500 car parks worldwide

Processing of personal data   
VINCI Park undertakes to respect the confidential nature of the personal data visitors enter into its Internet site. This notice describes the type of information VINCI Park may collect during your visit to its Internet site as well as the way in which this information will subsequently be used. Certain personal data recorded on our server are data you voluntarily disclose when filling out the on-line forms while other data are collected automatically.   
1\. PASSIVE DATA COLLECTION   
VINCI Park makes every effort to regularly improve its site. During your visit VINCI Park collects certain data automatically:   
o Your IP address. Your Internet Provider allocates an IP-address to your computer so that you can access the Internet. As this address changes each time you connect, it is generally accepted that you cannot be identified by this information.

o The address of the Internet Site which connects you directly to our Internet site.   
o The date and time of your visit and the pages you have consulted.   
o The operating system of your computer and your browser software.   
Our site can use cookies. These little files which are stored on your computer allow us to simplify your access to our services. The site cookies do not contain any data which may personally identify you. Moreover, they have been designed in such a way that only VINCI Park is in a position to use them. You can prevent registration of these “cookies” by adjusting your computer configuration.   
2\. USE OF COLLECTED DATA   
VINCI Park only uses the data collected to respond to the expectations of the visitors to its site. VINCI Park will only use the data for the purpose indicated at the time you provided them. Any personal data you have submitted to VINCI Park are strictly for internal use only. As a result, VINCI Park will not disclose, sell, lease or transfer personal data to other companies or entities.   
3\. INFORMATION PROTECTION   
VINCI Park has provided specific resources to store personal data securely so that they are protected against loss, change or hacking. The storage systems are only accessible to a limited number of authorized persons.   
4\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION   
Any personal data asked for (name, address, speciality, e-mail address) are used to employ individualisation functions. Refusal to submit such information does not have any adverse effects. There is however a possibility that certain functions may not be accessible or that the information you seek cannot be supplied. Pursuant to the legislation on data collection, files and personal freedom, VINCI Park can erase or modify any data you have provided at any time and upon simple request. Should you wish to check, amend, rectify or have your personal data erased, simply send a request to that effect to VINCI Park – Bijenstraat 21, B-9051 Sint-Denijs-Westrem. VINCI Park reserves the right to amend the aforementioned operational rules of the Internet site at any time. This notice does not imply any contractual or other type of relationship between VINCI Park and visitors to its Internet site or their respective rightful claimants.
